<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Swim England North East</title>
	<atom:link href="https://asaner.org.uk/feed/?rand_id=1577894012" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://asaner.org.uk</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 08:20:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	
	<item>
		<title>Swim England North East Regional Office Christmas Closure</title>
		<link>https://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-north-east-regional-office-christmas-closure/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Small]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Clubs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Disability Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Masters Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Northumberland and Durham]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Officials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Open Water Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SwimMark]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Synchronised Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Water Polo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Workforce]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://asaner.org.uk/?p=20200</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>The Swim England North East Regional Office will be closed from 2pm on Thursday 19th December 2019 until 9am on Monday 6th January 2020. The Region wishes all it’s members and partners a very Happy Christmas and we look forwards to working with you again in the New Year.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-north-east-regional-office-christmas-closure/">Swim England North East Regional Office Christmas Closure</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>The Swim England North East Regional Office will be closed from 2pm on Thursday 19</b><b>th</b><b> December 2019 until 9am on Monday 6</b><b>th</b><b> January 2020.</b></p>
<p><b>The Region wishes all it’s members and partners a very Happy Christmas and we look forwards to working with you again in the New Year.</b></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-north-east-regional-office-christmas-closure/">Swim England North East Regional Office Christmas Closure</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>North East Region teams dominate at Scottish National and Open Diving Championship 2019</title>
		<link>https://asaner.org.uk/north-east-region-teams-dominate-at-scottish-national-and-open-diving-championship-2019/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 08:11:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[David Parry]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Diving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://asaner.org.uk/?p=20316</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Divers from three clubs in the North East region took part in the Scottish National and Open Diving Championship in the auspicious Royal Commonwealth Pool in Edinburgh from 6th to 9th December.  The 39 divers – representing City of Sheffield Diving Club, City of Leeds Diving Club and City of Bradford Esprit – won an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk/north-east-region-teams-dominate-at-scottish-national-and-open-diving-championship-2019/">North East Region teams dominate at Scottish National and Open Diving Championship 2019</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Divers from three clubs in the North East region took part in the Scottish National and Open Diving Championship in the auspicious Royal Commonwealth Pool in Edinburgh from 6th to 9th December.  The 39 divers – representing City of Sheffield Diving Club, City of Leeds Diving Club and City of Bradford Esprit – won an impressive 28 medals between them over the four days of high level competition.</p>
<p>The first medals came in the Women’s 3m synchro competition on Day 1.  Elizabeth Powley of Leeds, with her partner Clara Kerr of Aberdeen Diving Club, won gold, while Amelia Scott and Sephora Ford of Sheffield took the bronze.</p>
<p>Day 2 saw an amazing 17 divers reach the finals of their events.<br />
Gold medals were won by Callie Eaglestone of Leeds in the Girls A 1m, Lewis Neilson of Sheffield in the Boys C Platform and Yasmin Harper of Sheffield in the Women’s 3m.<br />
Silver medals went to Jake Passmore of Leeds in the Boys B 1m, Joe Stocking of Leeds in the Boys A Platform, Jordan Houlden of Sheffield in the Men’s 3m and Chloe Johnson of Leeds in the Girls B Platform.<br />
Winning bronze medals were Richelle Houlden in the Girls A 1m, Etta Dodsworth in the Girls C 1m and Grace Ally in the Girls B Platform, all diving for Sheffield.</p>
<p>On the third day, 14 divers reached finals and won 8 medals in total.<br />
Gold went to Etta Dodsworth on Girls C Platform and to Chloe Johnson in the Girls B 3m.<br />
Winning silver were Yasmin Harper in the Women’s 1m and Lewis Neilson in the Boys C 3m, while bronze medals were won by Jaeda Sharman of Leeds in the Girls C Platform and Jack Burrows of Sheffield in the Boys B Platform.<br />
In the team event, in which mixed sex pairs each perform two dives and one dive in synchro, the gold was won by Elizabeth Powley and Jake Passmore of Leeds, with the silver going to Joe Stocking and Chloe Johnson, also of Leeds.</p>
<p>The final day saw 14 divers reaching finals and winning 7 more medals.<br />
The only gold of the day was won by Jake Passmore in the Boys B 3m event.<br />
Silver medals were won by Chloe Johnson in the Women’s Platform event, Jaeda Sharman in the Girls C 3m and Callie Eaglestone in the Girls A 3m.<br />
Finally, bronze medals went to Joseph Nicol of Bradford in the Boys A 1m, Elizabeth Powley in the Girls A 3m and Oscar Willcox of Sheffield in the Boys C 1m.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-20321" src="https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/ScottishNationalDivers2019a-300x225.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="225" srcset="https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/ScottishNationalDivers2019a-300x225.jpg 300w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/ScottishNationalDivers2019a-768x576.jpg 768w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/ScottishNationalDivers2019a-705x529.jpg 705w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/ScottishNationalDivers2019a-450x338.jpg 450w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/ScottishNationalDivers2019a.jpg 960w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /> <img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-20322" src="https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/ScottishNationalDivers2019b-300x225.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="225" srcset="https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/ScottishNationalDivers2019b-300x225.jpg 300w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/ScottishNationalDivers2019b-768x576.jpg 768w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/ScottishNationalDivers2019b-705x529.jpg 705w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/ScottishNationalDivers2019b-450x338.jpg 450w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/ScottishNationalDivers2019b.jpg 960w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /> <img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-20323" src="https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/ScottishNationalDivers2019c-300x225.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="225" srcset="https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/ScottishNationalDivers2019c-300x225.jpg 300w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/ScottishNationalDivers2019c-768x576.jpg 768w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/ScottishNationalDivers2019c-705x529.jpg 705w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/ScottishNationalDivers2019c-450x338.jpg 450w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/ScottishNationalDivers2019c.jpg 960w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /></p>
<p>All divers should be congratulated for their efforts and also include: representing Sheffield &#8211; Oliver Hoban, Joseph Pashley, Adam Charity, Isaac Trueman-Marsden, Elliott Dillon, Declan Rogan, Nathaniel Greig, Arthur Turner-Rowe, Harrison Hartley, Archie Biggin, Millie-Rose Hartley, Katie Garner and Hannah Blake; representing Leeds &#8211; Sophie Robbins and Holly Waxman; representing Bradford &#8211; Koben O-Driscoll, Lara Bradley, Joseph Verity, Megan Beasley and Owen Taylor.</p>
<p>The final total for the North East region was 9 gold medals, 10 silver and 9 bronze.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk/north-east-region-teams-dominate-at-scottish-national-and-open-diving-championship-2019/">North East Region teams dominate at Scottish National and Open Diving Championship 2019</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>‘Inspirational’ Kingston Upon Hull coach Graham Martin wins BBC Unsung Hero regional award</title>
		<link>https://asaner.org.uk/inspirational-kingston-upon-hull-coach-graham-martin-wins-bbc-unsung-hero-regional-award/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 13:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Small]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Swimming]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://asaner.org.uk/?p=20290</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Inspirational swimming coach Graham Martin said he was flabbergasted to be named the BBC Unsung Hero for the East Yorkshire and Lincolnshire region. Graham, who has volunteered at the club for 20 years, admitted the honour came as a complete shock – and said it was an award for everyone associated with Kingston Upon Hull [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk/inspirational-kingston-upon-hull-coach-graham-martin-wins-bbc-unsung-hero-regional-award/">‘Inspirational’ Kingston Upon Hull coach Graham Martin wins BBC Unsung Hero regional award</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Inspirational swimming coach Graham Martin said he was flabbergasted to be named the BBC Unsung Hero for the East Yorkshire and Lincolnshire region.</p>
<p>Graham, who has volunteered at the club for 20 years, admitted the honour came as a complete shock – and said it was an award for everyone associated with Kingston Upon Hull SC.</p>
<p>The 61-year-old mechanic said: “<em>This has come out of the blue. Winning the regional award is massive for me. It’s like winning a Willy Wonka golden ticket. For people like me, these things do not come along very often. It’s a golden opportunity and, at the end of the day, it’s for everyone back at the club.”</em></p>
<p>Graham said swimming has always been a part of his life and he first got involved with Kingston when his daughter started lessons.</p>
<p><em>“They got me hook, line and sinker,”</em> he laughed. <em>“The next thing, I’m a fully qualified coach. Through my life, I’ve always been a very sporty person. I used to swim when I was younger but not to the standards of the swimmers I coach now. I had a motorbike accident and to recoup, I got back into the pool and started swimming. I can’t run so it was part of my exercise regime and I have always loved it. Now I’m a coach, I can’t get in the water!”</em></p>
<p>For five nights a week and whenever galas are held, Graham is poolside – but he wouldn’t have it any other way. And he praised his partner, Margaret, for her support while he is away from home at training and events</p>
<p><em>“Margaret has been the rock behind me,”</em> he said. <em>“All us volunteers are just a cog in the wheel and we all have to work together to develop every swimmer&#8221;.</em></p>
<p>More of the story can be found on the <a href="https://www.swimming.org/swimengland/graham-martin-unsung-hero/?utm_campaign=SwimEngland&amp;utm_medium=GrahamMartinBBCUnsungHeroutm_source=NewsBlade">Swim England website</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk/inspirational-kingston-upon-hull-coach-graham-martin-wins-bbc-unsung-hero-regional-award/">‘Inspirational’ Kingston Upon Hull coach Graham Martin wins BBC Unsung Hero regional award</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mental Health Awareness</title>
		<link>https://asaner.org.uk/mental-health-awareness/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 13:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[David Parry]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Clubs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Disability Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Masters Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Synchronised Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Water Polo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Workforce]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://asaner.org.uk/?p=20282</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Swim England have a We&#8217;ve&#8230;.Got UR Back scheme to support positive mental health. The scheme focuses on Awareness, Education and Training opportunities: Further information is available at Swim England Mental Health, Awareness and Education A Swim England recorded webinar is available to view by clicking here.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk/mental-health-awareness/">Mental Health Awareness</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Swim England have a We&#8217;ve&#8230;.Got UR Back scheme to support positive mental health.</p>
<p>The scheme focuses on Awareness, Education and Training opportunities:</p>
<p>Further information is available at <a href="https://asaner.org.uk/mdocs-posts/swim-england-mental-health-awareness-and-education/">Swim England Mental Health, Awareness and Education</a></p>
<p>A Swim England recorded webinar is available to view by <a href="https://zoom.us/recording/share/p7IPaJzeKxZ39OziKHsotiMnrbotlxSBd0r4jHxDD6awIumekTziMw?startTime=1575896885000">clicking here.</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk/mental-health-awareness/">Mental Health Awareness</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>U14 Boys Water Polo Inter-Regional Competition</title>
		<link>https://asaner.org.uk/u14-boys-water-polo-inter-regional-competition/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 11:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[David Parry]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Water Polo]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://asaner.org.uk/?p=20219</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>The teams Head Coach Richard Cousins reports: The &#8217;06 Steelers travelled to Walsall for the U14 Boys Inter-Regional competition. This was anticipated as a tough competition because very few of the players had ever been to a competition at this level. First up was the challenge from the Welsh Dragons. The Welsh got a good [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk/u14-boys-water-polo-inter-regional-competition/">U14 Boys Water Polo Inter-Regional Competition</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The teams Head Coach Richard Cousins reports:</p>
<p>The &#8217;06 Steelers travelled to Walsall for the U14 Boys Inter-Regional competition. This was anticipated as a tough competition because very few of the players had ever been to a competition at this level.</p>
<p>First up was the challenge from the Welsh Dragons. The Welsh got a good start with the Steelers not able to keep pace with the quick counter-attacking opposition, going down 10-3.  Second game of the day was against South East. The NE boys got stuck into this match and restricted the SE team to fewer opportunities, while being unable to convert the chances they created. NE finally went down 7-3.</p>
<p>The third and final game of the day was against the eventual silver medalists from West Midlands. The NE boys were once again heavily punished on the counter-attack by a quick thinking and faster swimming team.</p>
<p>The end of the first day and a very hard introduction to the next level up in junior polo. It was clear to the NE players that critical swim fitness was not at the standard it needs to be. What was encouraging was that every player gave everything they had in every match.</p>
<p>After a good nights rest the NE Steelers resumed on Sunday morning playing out the fixtures 10-12 place playoffs. First match against East and despite going behind early on the team rolled up their sleeves, closed down the opposition and converted the chances they created. Final whistle saw the Steelers complete their first victory 8-7. The final match was against NW Ravens, a team confident they could dominate the Steelers. Once again NE went behind to some long range efforts from NW. Chances were created by NE but nothing really troubling the Ravens keeper. With the scores level going into the final seconds NW countered, the pass from the GK was overthrown and gave the Steelers GK, Harry Wallbank the chance to swim out and steal. Only 3 secs remained on the clock as Harry kicked out of the water and shot from 8m inside his own half. As the ball crashed into the back of the net the buzzer sounded for the end of the game. A second win 4-3.</p>
<p>The team may not have emulated the tremendous win by the girls recently, but they now understand what they need to do to progress, and to a player have said they intend to do that work. A tough weekend clearly but also some very valuable lessons have been learnt.</p>
<p>Congratulations to Harry Wallbank for his MVP performance.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-20225" src="https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/79799695_1395910550563324_4990031353979338752_o.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="200" srcset="https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/79799695_1395910550563324_4990031353979338752_o.jpg 200w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/79799695_1395910550563324_4990031353979338752_o-80x80.jpg 80w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/79799695_1395910550563324_4990031353979338752_o-36x36.jpg 36w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/79799695_1395910550563324_4990031353979338752_o-180x180.jpg 180w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/79799695_1395910550563324_4990031353979338752_o-100x100.jpg 100w" sizes="(max-width: 200px) 100vw, 200px" /></p>
<p>Thanks to all those involved in providing the team with this opportunity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk/u14-boys-water-polo-inter-regional-competition/">U14 Boys Water Polo Inter-Regional Competition</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>North East Swimmers Compete at Swim England National Winter Championships</title>
		<link>https://asaner.org.uk/north-east-swimmers-compete-at-swim-england-national-winter-championships/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 09:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Small]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Swimming]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://asaner.org.uk/?p=20206</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>On Thursday, swimmers from across the North East travelled to Ponds Forge in Sheffield to compete in the Swim England National Winter Championships. Once again, swimmers from within the region demonstrated their talent with many swimmers collecting multiple medals across numerous events. Many congratulations to everyone who competed and thank you to their clubs, coaches [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk/north-east-swimmers-compete-at-swim-england-national-winter-championships/">North East Swimmers Compete at Swim England National Winter Championships</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On Thursday, swimmers from across the North East travelled to Ponds Forge in Sheffield to compete in the Swim England National Winter Championships.</p>
<p>Once again, swimmers from within the region demonstrated their talent with many swimmers collecting multiple medals across numerous events.</p>
<p>Many congratulations to everyone who competed and thank you to their clubs, coaches and support team for all the work that you do.</p>
<p>Full results from the championships <a href="https://www.swimmingresults.org.uk/swimming/results/2019/sesc19/">can be viewed here.</a> Reports from Swim England on the Championships <a href="https://www.swimming.org/sport/tag/national-winter-championships-2019/">can also be viewed here</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk/north-east-swimmers-compete-at-swim-england-national-winter-championships/">North East Swimmers Compete at Swim England National Winter Championships</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Swim England National Awards 2019 roll of honour</title>
		<link>https://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-national-awards-2019-roll-of-honour/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 13:07:31 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Linda Tjaguns]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Workforce]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://asaner.org.uk/?p=20180</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>A total of 34 awards were presented during the ceremony at Birmingham University’s Great Hall on 30th November, 2019. The Awards recognised the vast contribution made by individuals and organisations from all aquatic sports. We are delighted that the North East Region received 2 Bronze awards:- Youth Volunteer of the Year Award &#8211; Albany Thompson [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-national-awards-2019-roll-of-honour/">Swim England National Awards 2019 roll of honour</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A total of 34 awards were presented during the ceremony at Birmingham University’s Great Hall on 30th November, 2019.</p>
<p>The Awards recognised the vast contribution made by individuals and organisations from all aquatic sports.</p>
<p>We are delighted that the North East Region received 2 Bronze awards:-</p>
<p>Youth Volunteer of the Year Award &#8211; Albany Thompson</p>
<p><img class="size-medium wp-image-20187" src="https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Albany-Thompson-NE-300x195.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="195" srcset="https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Albany-Thompson-NE-300x195.jpg 300w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Albany-Thompson-NE-1030x669.jpg 1030w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Albany-Thompson-NE-768x499.jpg 768w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Albany-Thompson-NE-1536x998.jpg 1536w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Albany-Thompson-NE-2048x1330.jpg 2048w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Albany-Thompson-NE-1500x974.jpg 1500w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Albany-Thompson-NE-705x458.jpg 705w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Albany-Thompson-NE-450x292.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /></p>
<p>Technical Official of the Year Award &#8211; Samantha Travis</p>
<p><img class="size-medium wp-image-20188" src="https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Samantha-NE-300x203.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="203" srcset="https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Samantha-NE-300x203.jpg 300w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Samantha-NE-1030x695.jpg 1030w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Samantha-NE-768x518.jpg 768w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Samantha-NE-1536x1037.jpg 1536w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Samantha-NE-2048x1383.jpg 2048w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Samantha-NE-1500x1013.jpg 1500w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Samantha-NE-705x476.jpg 705w, https://asaner.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Samantha-NE-450x304.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-national-awards-2019-roll-of-honour/">Swim England National Awards 2019 roll of honour</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>National Para Swimming Championships</title>
		<link>https://asaner.org.uk/national-para-swimming-championships-2/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 15:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Small]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Disability Swimming]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://asaner.org.uk/?p=20162</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Well done to the swimmers, coaches and volunteers from the Swim England North East Region who were involved in the National Para Swimming Championships held in Manchester over the weekend. A full review of the event and the race results are available by clicking here: 2019 results. &#160;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk/national-para-swimming-championships-2/">National Para Swimming Championships</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Well done to the swimmers, coaches and volunteers from the Swim England North East Region who were involved in the National Para Swimming Championships held in Manchester over the weekend.</p>
<p>A full review of the event and the race results are available by clicking here: <a href="https://www.swimmingresults.org.uk/disability/results/2019/aalc/">2019 results</a>.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk/national-para-swimming-championships-2/">National Para Swimming Championships</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gold’s for City of Sheffield’s Maisie Bond at Camo Invitational Diving Competition</title>
		<link>https://asaner.org.uk/golds-for-city-of-sheffields-maisie-bond-at-camo-invitational-diving-competition/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 14:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Small]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Diving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://asaner.org.uk/?p=20157</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Over the past couple of days, Swim England divers have been enjoying success at the Camo Invitational in Canada. On the first day of the competition, City of Sheffield’s Maisie Bond set a new personal best as she joined Crystal Palace’s Jack Jefford on top of the podium at the Claude Robillard Sports Complex, in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk/golds-for-city-of-sheffields-maisie-bond-at-camo-invitational-diving-competition/">Gold’s for City of Sheffield’s Maisie Bond at Camo Invitational Diving Competition</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Over the past couple of days, Swim England divers have been enjoying success at the Camo Invitational in Canada.</p>
<p>On the first day of the competition, City of Sheffield’s Maisie Bond set a new personal best as she joined Crystal Palace’s Jack Jefford on top of the podium at the Claude Robillard Sports Complex, in Montreal.</p>
<p>Maise was 35.25 points ahead of second-placed Heloa Camelo, of Brazil, after scoring an impressive 283.95 in the Girls’ C 1m Springboard. Her team mate, Jenna Davison was 19th in the preliminary round and missed out on a place in the final.</p>
<p>Suzie Collins, Swim England Talent Development Officer Diving, said: <em>“It’s been a great opening day for the team and fantastic to hear the national anthem ringing around the Claude Robillard Sports Complex twice.</em></p>
<p><em>We’re really settled in now and looking forward to getting the Group Bs on the platform.”</em></p>
<p>On the second day of competition, Masie was once again on the top of the podium, leading from start to finish in the Girls’ C Platform competition, saving her best dive until last.</p>
<p>Her back two-and-a-half somersaults tucked from the 7m board earned her nines and ensured she smashed through the 300-point mark.</p>
<p>Maisie’s total of 305.25 was 42.45 points ahead of Germany’s Lena Philin Schneider, who took the silver medal while Jenna Davison was sixth on 298.60.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk/golds-for-city-of-sheffields-maisie-bond-at-camo-invitational-diving-competition/">Gold’s for City of Sheffield’s Maisie Bond at Camo Invitational Diving Competition</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>North East Region U14 Girls Water Polo Team &#8211; Swim England Inter-Regional Champions 2019</title>
		<link>https://asaner.org.uk/u14-girls-water-polo-team-swim-england-inter-regional-champions-2019/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 10:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[David Parry]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Clubs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Water Polo]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://asaner.org.uk/?p=20141</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>The North East 2006+ Girls team competed at the Inter Regions in Walsall on 30th November and the 1st Dec 2020. The team’s Head Coach, Kevin Swainson, reports: “We had our team talk before the first match and set out our tactics for the weekend.  I felt that if we played as a team, not [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk/u14-girls-water-polo-team-swim-england-inter-regional-champions-2019/">North East Region U14 Girls Water Polo Team &#8211; Swim England Inter-Regional Champions 2019</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The North East 2006+ Girls team competed at the Inter Regions in Walsall on 30th November and the 1<sup>st</sup> Dec 2020.</p>
<p>The team’s Head Coach, Kevin Swainson, reports:</p>
<p><em>“We had our team talk before the first match and set out our tactics for the weekend.  I felt that if we played as a team, not as individuals, we had a very good chance of a medal.</em></p>
<p><em>Going into the competition I was confident in our team, with two very capable Centre Backs in Connie and Amelia I felt that we could ball line press in defence and put allot of pressure on the attacking team. We had worked hard on this in the last few weeks and it paid dividends at the weekend only conceding 17 goals in the whole tournament and causing the attacking teams allot of problems. </em></p>
<p><em>This was complimented by our scoring capabilities; we played excellent as a team in attack with very good, unselfish water polo from the whole team resulting in every single player scoring during the weekend.   This included taking advantage of the new rules and allowing our</em> <em>goalkeeper to join the attack.  Severn came out to attack three times and we scored on all three occasions including two goals from our goalkeeper Severn which I think was one of the highlights of the whole weekend for the whole team. We managed 75 goals in 6 matches, that is 17 more than any other team in the competition.</em></p>
<p><em>The semi-final against North West was a fantastic match and in fairness the score did not reflect how close the match was, the girls started fantastic against the tournaments number one seed and showed grit and determination for the full match.</em></p>
<p><em>The final was a re-match of our earlier encounter with Ireland, Ireland had won the first time 7-4 but we felt that this could be a result that we could turn around.  Ireland came at us very strong, frustrating our players in attack and forcing us to rush and make mistakes.  With the score line at 5-2 down with only 3 minutes left on the clock some teams would have given up but the girls showed grit, determination and heart to score 3 times in the last 3 mins to take the match to penalties.</em></p>
<p><em>No one likes a penalty shootout but the girls although extremely nervous performed fantastic, good penalties taken by all the players and Severn managing to pull off two fantastic saves won us the title.</em></p>
<p><em>Congratulations to Laura who won team MVP, Tournament MVP and top goal scorer in the tournament.</em></p>
<p><em>Special thanks to Gabby, Liz and Michelle for your help at the weekend and for your assistance in the weeks building up to the competition.</em></p>
<p><em>Thank you to the parents for your support during the weekend, without your support we would not be the team we are.</em></p>
<p><em>And last but probably the most important, thank you to the players for the effort you all put it to make this weekend such a success and so enjoyable.  The team not only worked well together in the pool they all got on so well outside the pool and on behalf of myself, gabby and Liz I would like to wish the team a long and successful future in the sport.&#8221;</em></p>
<p>The Team included:</p>
<p>Severn Annakin &#8211; St bede&#8217;s and st joseph&#8217;s catholic college<br />
Amelia Hendesron &#8211; Sedgefield WPC<br />
Ruby Taylor &#8211; City of Sheffield WPC<br />
Connie Swainson &#8211; Rotherham Metro WPC<br />
Lilly Pryce &#8211; St bede&#8217;s and st joseph&#8217;s catholic college<br />
Lola Carver-Brown &#8211; Rotherham Metro<br />
Caitlin Urqhuart &#8211; City of Sheffield WPC<br />
Laura Skelton &#8211; Rotherham Metro<br />
Amelia Brooksbank &#8211; St bede&#8217;s and st joseph&#8217;s catholic college<br />
Isobel Olcer &#8211; Rotherham Metro WPC</p>
<p><strong><u>Results</u></strong></p>
<p>North east Steelers     26 – 0 Wales</p>
<p>North east Steelers     4 – 7 Ireland</p>
<p>North east Steelers     16 – 0 East Midland</p>
<p>North east Steelers     14 – 1 South East</p>
<p><strong><u>Semi Final </u></strong></p>
<p>North east Steelers     10 – 4 North West Thunder</p>
<p><strong><u>Final</u></strong></p>
<p>North east Steelers     8 – 6 Ireland (After Penalties)</p>
<p>Well done, congratulations and thanks to all involved for your achievement.</p>
<p style="line-height: 115%; margin: 0cm 0cm 10.0pt 0cm;">
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk/u14-girls-water-polo-team-swim-england-inter-regional-champions-2019/">North East Region U14 Girls Water Polo Team &#8211; Swim England Inter-Regional Champions 2019</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
