<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Swim England North East</title>
	<atom:link href="http://asaner.org.uk/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://asaner.org.uk</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 20:43:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	
	<item>
		<title>PLACES STILL AVAILABLE &#8211; Thursday 11th July &#8211; 6:45pm &#8211; SwimMark Essential Club Information Workshop ONLINE</title>
		<link>http://asaner.org.uk/places-still-available-thursday-31st-january-645pm-swimmark-essential-club-information-workshop-online-2-2/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 20:43:25 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Daniel Ramm]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Clubs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Disability Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Masters Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Open Water Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SwimMark]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Synchronised Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Water Polo]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://asaner.org.uk/?p=18593</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>On Thursday 11th July 2019 at 6:45pm there will be a SwimMark Essential Club Information Workshop held online. The workshop is free and open to all clubs. &#160; The aim of the workshop is to provide information to clubs looking start or complete their SwimMark essential accreditation and will cover the following areas: &#160; Overview [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/places-still-available-thursday-31st-january-645pm-swimmark-essential-club-information-workshop-online-2-2/">PLACES STILL AVAILABLE &#8211; Thursday 11th July &#8211; 6:45pm &#8211; SwimMark Essential Club Information Workshop ONLINE</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On Thursday 11th July 2019 at 6:45pm there will be a SwimMark Essential Club Information Workshop held online. The workshop is free and open to all clubs.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The aim of the workshop is to provide information to clubs looking start or complete their SwimMark essential accreditation and will cover the following areas:</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>Overview of the SwimMark accreditation – accreditation and benefits.</li>
<li>Guide to using the SwimMark portal and the accreditation process.</li>
<li>Run-through of the evidence required for accreditation.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>There will also be an opportunity to ask any questions you may have specific to your club or the SwimMark process.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>If you would be interested in attending or have any questions, please can you email Swim England Club Development Officer, Daniel Ramm on <a href="mailto:daniel.ramm@swimming.org">daniel.ramm@swimming.org</a>  with your name and contact email address, so he can reserve you a place and send you joining instructions.</p>
<p style="font-style: italic;">Post expires at 10:18pm on Wednesday August 7th, 2019</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/places-still-available-thursday-31st-january-645pm-swimmark-essential-club-information-workshop-online-2-2/">PLACES STILL AVAILABLE &#8211; Thursday 11th July &#8211; 6:45pm &#8211; SwimMark Essential Club Information Workshop ONLINE</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Young North East Swimmers represent Britain in Kazan</title>
		<link>http://asaner.org.uk/young-north-east-swimmers-represent-britain-in-kazan/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 12:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Small]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Clubs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Swimming]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://asaner.org.uk/?p=18582</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>City of Sheffield Swim Squad’s Charlie Brown and City of Leeds Rebecca Clynes are in Kazan in Russia as part of a squad of 30 British swimmers testing themselves against strong international competition at the LEN European Junior Swimming Championships. The competition starts today, Wednesday 3rd July 2019 and continues until Sunday 7th July 2019. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/young-north-east-swimmers-represent-britain-in-kazan/">Young North East Swimmers represent Britain in Kazan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>City of Sheffield Swim Squad’s Charlie Brown and City of Leeds Rebecca Clynes are in Kazan in Russia as part of a squad of 30 British swimmers testing themselves against strong international competition at the LEN European Junior Swimming Championships.</p>
<p>The competition starts today, Wednesday 3rd July 2019 and continues until Sunday 7th July 2019.</p>
<p>Following the<a href="https://www.swimming.org/diving/tag/european-junior-championships-2019/"> success of the British diving team at the Kazan Aquatics Palace last week</a>, the swimmers have the chance to take the next step in their careers, with plenty of eyes on the talent of the future ahead of this month’s World Championships in Korea.</p>
<p>Charlie is also one of 5 swimmers who will feature at <a href="https://www.swimming.org/sport/gb-team-world-european-juniors/">next month’s World Junior Championships in Budapest.</a> Best of luck Charlie and Rebecca!</p>
<p>Main photo: <a title="British Swimming on Twitter" href="https://twitter.com/britishswimming/status/1145958082180255744" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">British Swimming/Twitter</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/young-north-east-swimmers-represent-britain-in-kazan/">Young North East Swimmers represent Britain in Kazan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Swim England North East Region ACM 2019 &#8211; Vice President &#038; Delegates to ASA Council Nomination Form</title>
		<link>http://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-north-east-region-acm-2019-vice-president-delegates-to-asa-council-nomination-form/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 08:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Linda Tjaguns]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Clubs]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://asaner.org.uk/?p=18577</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>The Annual Council Meeting of the Swim England North East Region will be held on Sunday 8th September 2019 at 11 a.m. at The Bridge Hotel, Wetherby, LS22 5DY. Nominations are invited for the role of North East Region Vice President 2019-20 and Delegates to ASA Council 2019. Click here for nomination form</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-north-east-region-acm-2019-vice-president-delegates-to-asa-council-nomination-form/">Swim England North East Region ACM 2019 &#8211; Vice President &#038; Delegates to ASA Council Nomination Form</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Annual Council Meeting of the Swim England North East Region will be held on Sunday 8th September 2019 at 11 a.m. at The Bridge Hotel, Wetherby, LS22 5DY.</p>
<p>Nominations are invited for the role of North East Region Vice President 2019-20 and Delegates to ASA Council 2019.</p>
<p><a href="http://asaner.org.uk/mdocs-posts/north-east-region-acm-nomination-form-2019/">Click here for nomination form</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-north-east-region-acm-2019-vice-president-delegates-to-asa-council-nomination-form/">Swim England North East Region ACM 2019 &#8211; Vice President &#038; Delegates to ASA Council Nomination Form</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Open Water Championship Results 2019</title>
		<link>http://asaner.org.uk/open-water-championship-results-2019/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 08:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Small]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Open Water Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Swimming]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://asaner.org.uk/?p=18571</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>The results for the 2019 Open Water Festival held on the 29th June 2019 in Salford, which incorporated the North East Regional Championships can be found here: 2019 Open Water Festival Results. Many congratulations to all the swimmers who took part, it was a lovely weekend for open water swimming. &#160;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/open-water-championship-results-2019/">Open Water Championship Results 2019</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The results for the 2019 Open Water Festival held on the 29th June 2019 in Salford, which incorporated the North East Regional Championships can be found here: <a href="https://swimnorthwest.org/results/OpenWater/2019-Open-Water-Results.pdf">2019 Open Water Festival Results</a>.</p>
<p>Many congratulations to all the swimmers who took part, it was a lovely weekend for open water swimming.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/open-water-championship-results-2019/">Open Water Championship Results 2019</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Swim England North East Region &#8211; Board of Trustees vacancies</title>
		<link>http://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-north-east-region-board-of-trustee-vacancies/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 12:36:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Linda Tjaguns]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Clubs]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://asaner.org.uk/?p=18562</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>The Annual Council Meeting of the Swim England North East Region will be held on Sunday, 8 September 2019 at 11.00 a.m. at The Bridge Hotel, Wetherby, LS22 5DY From 1st October 2019 Swim England North East Region will be known as SWIM ENGLAND NORTH EAST LIMITED. As a result of Incorporation, the Board of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-north-east-region-board-of-trustee-vacancies/">Swim England North East Region &#8211; Board of Trustees vacancies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Annual Council Meeting of the Swim England North East Region will be held on Sunday, 8 September 2019 at 11.00 a.m. at The Bridge Hotel, Wetherby, LS22 5DY</p>
<p><em>From 1<sup>st</sup> October 2019 Swim England North East Region will be known as SWIM ENGLAND NORTH EAST LIMITED.</em></p>
<p><em>As a result of Incorporation, the Board of Trustees has 5 vacancies (applicants must be members of the ASA and of an Affiliated Club)</em></p>
<p><em>Anyone wishing to apply for the position of Trustee should email a covering letter/C.V. to the Swim England North East Regional Office – <a href="mailto:linda.tjaguns@swimming.org">linda.tjaguns@swimming.org</a> by 29 July 2019.</em></p>
<p>Applicants may be invited to attend an informal interview, appointments will take place at the ACM in September 2019.</p>
<p><a href="http://asaner.org.uk/mdocs-posts/board-of-trustees-job-description/">Board of Trustees Job Description</a></p>
<p style="font-style: italic;">Post expires at 5:00pm on Monday July 29th, 2019</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-north-east-region-board-of-trustee-vacancies/">Swim England North East Region &#8211; Board of Trustees vacancies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Swimmers Attend Second Northumberland and Durham Swimming Camp</title>
		<link>http://asaner.org.uk/swimmers-attend-second-northumberland-and-durham-swimming-camp/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 18:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Small]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[NER Performance and Development Programmes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Northumberland and Durham]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[talent]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://asaner.org.uk/?p=18553</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>On Saturday 29th June 2019, thirty-two swimmers from across the county attend the second of three county training camps to be held this year at Consett Leisure Centre. The camps form part of the Northumberland and Durham and Swim England talent pathway and provide swimmers within an opportunity to develop their technical, tactical, physical and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/swimmers-attend-second-northumberland-and-durham-swimming-camp/">Swimmers Attend Second Northumberland and Durham Swimming Camp</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On Saturday 29th June 2019, thirty-two swimmers from across the county attend the second of three county training camps to be held this year at Consett Leisure Centre.</p>
<p>The camps form part of the Northumberland and Durham and Swim England talent pathway and provide swimmers within an opportunity to develop their technical, tactical, physical and psychological skills with swimmers of a similar age and ability from across the county. The camps also provide an opportunity for swimmers to work with different coaches and to train in different environments.</p>
<p>As part of the camp, swimmers completed two pool sessions, as well as land based sessions and workshops. These sessions were overseen by the camps head coach Chris Leighton (BOSSS), supported by Howard Leighton as Team Manager (BOSSS) and skills coaches Keith Hall (Richmond Dales), Emily Betham (Tynemouth), Tim Maddison (Aqua Force), Jonny Carlisle (City of Sunderland) and Michele Davison (Newcastle Swim Team).</p>
<p>The next camp will be on the 14th September at Consett Leisure Centre. There is an open invite for coaches and Team Managers within the county to attend the camp as an observer for a development opportunity. If you would like to attend, please contact Sarah Small on <a href="mailto:sarah.small@swimnortheast.org" data-slimstat="5">sarah.small@swimnortheast.org</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/swimmers-attend-second-northumberland-and-durham-swimming-camp/">Swimmers Attend Second Northumberland and Durham Swimming Camp</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Swim England update for SwimMark Clubs – June 2019</title>
		<link>http://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-update-for-swimmark-clubs-june-2019/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 13:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Small]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Clubs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Northumberland and Durham]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SwimMark]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Swimming]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://asaner.org.uk/?p=18550</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>During a previous Swim England Club Management Group meeting, a decision was made to compile an update following each quarterly meeting (March, June, September and December).  The following is the latest update:- SwimMark Updates:- Element 14 &#8211; Please find attached a copy of the revised guidance document, which outlines accepted training (face-to-face and online) for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-update-for-swimmark-clubs-june-2019/">Swim England update for SwimMark Clubs – June 2019</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>During a previous Swim England Club Management Group meeting, a decision was made to compile an update following each quarterly meeting (March, June, September and December).  The following is the latest update:-</p>
<p>SwimMark Updates:-</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Element 14</strong> &#8211; Please find attached a copy of the revised guidance document, which outlines <u>accepted</u> training (face-to-face and online) for SwimMark.</li>
<li><strong>SwimMark benefit</strong> &#8211; SwimMark clubs can now access three <u>free</u> bronze listings per year for coaching vacancies on the Careers in Aquatics website. To submit a vacancy, please go to <a href="https://www.swimming.org/careers/">org/careers</a> and visit the ‘Post a Job’ page. You will then need to enter the code SWMK19 plus your 4 character club code in the promotional box i.e. SWMK19SECL.</li>
<li><strong>SwimMark portal</strong> &#8211; There was recently a security message on the SwimMark portal and we therefore want to ensure clubs that the system is safe to use.</li>
</ul>
<p>General Updates:-</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Swim England Coaching &amp; Teaching Register</strong>:
<ul>
<li>We now have details for over 8,000 coaches and teachers listed on the register. This information will enable Swim England to support and communicate with those individuals that play a pivotal role in the development of our aquatic sports.  A newsletter was circulated to coaches early June and a teaching update is scheduled for w/c 1<sup>st</sup>  To ensure coaches and teachers receive these quarterly updates they must be listed on the register!</li>
<li>For more information about the register please visit: <a href="https://www.swimming.org/swimengland/coaching-teaching-register/">https://www.swimming.org/swimengland/coaching-teaching-register/</a></li>
<li>Please note that information from the register will be used to populate E13 in the future (i.e. from the December Panel/accreditation date) and it is therefore crucial to ensure that all SwimMark clubs have added their coaches and teachers, to avoid duplication of work and to ensure information is accurate. Additional information will be issued to clubs in due course.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Club Hub</strong> – a new Club Support Hub is available on the Swim England website &#8211; <a href="https://www.swimming.org/swimengland/clubs-home/">https://www.swimming.org/swimengland/clubs-home/</a>. Here clubs will find a wealth of information and resources to start, manage and develop your aquatics club.  Please note that new information will continue to be added to the Hub as and when required.</li>
<li><strong>Risk Assessment Portal</strong> – a new portal is currently being tested by 25 clubs, with an expected launch date of early 2020. More information will be circulated when available.</li>
<li><strong>Wavepower</strong> – a new version of Wavepower will be available in January 2020, with a free hard copy available for all Child Welfare Officers.</li>
<li><strong>Senior Coach Applications</strong> – The application process for the Senior Coach programme will open from the <strong>10<sup>th</sup> June 2019</strong>, closing on the <strong>4<sup>th</sup> August 2019</strong>. If coaches require more information please direct them to <a href="https://www.swimming.org/ios/course/1862">https://www.swimming.org/ios/course/1862</a></li>
<li><strong>Swim England Club Awards</strong> &#8211; six progressive club awards were launched in 2018 to help children make the transition from the Swim England Learn To Swim Programme to a club level swimmer. All six awards should be delivered by fully-qualified swimming coaches.  For further information please use the following link: <a href="https://www.swimming.org/sport/coaching-the-swimming-club-awards/">https://www.swimming.org/sport/coaching-the-swimming-club-awards/</a></li>
</ul>
<p>Thank you for your continued commitment to SwimMark!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-update-for-swimmark-clubs-june-2019/">Swim England update for SwimMark Clubs – June 2019</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Swim England National Age Group Diving Championships 2019</title>
		<link>http://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-national-age-group-diving-championships-2019/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 09:45:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[David Parry]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Clubs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://asaner.org.uk/?p=18537</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Congratulations to all the Teams from the North East Region who competed at the Swim England National Age Group Diving Championships . All North East Region Clubs went home with athletes who achieved top three individual performances. Well done to City of Sheffield Diving who were the overall winners. A full report is available at: [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-national-age-group-diving-championships-2019/">Swim England National Age Group Diving Championships 2019</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Congratulations to all the Teams from the North East Region who competed at the Swim England National Age Group Diving Championships . All North East Region Clubs went home with athletes who achieved top three individual performances.</p>
<p>Well done to City of Sheffield Diving who were the overall winners.</p>
<p>A full report is available at:<a href="https://www.swimming.org/diving/city-sheffield-top-club/"> https://www.swimming.org/diving/city-sheffield-top-club/</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-national-age-group-diving-championships-2019/">Swim England National Age Group Diving Championships 2019</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>North East Regional Swimming Camp takes place in Catterick</title>
		<link>http://asaner.org.uk/18531-2/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 10:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[David Parry]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Swimming]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://asaner.org.uk/?p=18531</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>The first of three Swim England North East Swimming Camps  took place in Catterick on Sunday 30th June 2019 for swimmers aged 12/13 years old. The camp forms part of the North East Region Performance Programme and will provide an opportunity for swimmers to develop their technical, tactical, physical and psychological skills with swimmers of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/18531-2/">North East Regional Swimming Camp takes place in Catterick</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The first of three Swim England North East Swimming Camps  took place in Catterick on Sunday 30th June 2019 for swimmers aged 12/13 years old.</p>
<p>The camp forms part of the North East Region Performance Programme and will provide an opportunity for swimmers to develop their technical, tactical, physical and psychological skills with swimmers of a similar age and ability from across the Region. The camps will also provide an opportunity for swimmers to work with different coaches and to train in different environments. The aim is for the camps to be a positive and rewarding experience, with the intention of them being a stepping-stone to progress to further camps in the future.</p>
<p>The camp is delivered with the assistance of a team of coaches and sport specialists who deliver the various sessions. Two additional camps take place later in the year.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/18531-2/">North East Regional Swimming Camp takes place in Catterick</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Swimming Coach CPD Opportunity Well Received in Stanley</title>
		<link>http://asaner.org.uk/swimming-coach-cpd-opportunity-well-received-in-stanley/</link>
				<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 18:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[David Parry]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Clubs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Swimming]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://asaner.org.uk/?p=18524</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Twenty coaches from across the Swim England North East Region attended a CPD opportunity which focused on supporting and developing  the nutrition and psychology needs of their athletes. The two sessions were delivered by specialists from the Swim England Talent Team. One coach commented, &#8220;Both presenters were very easy to follow and gave some useful [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/swimming-coach-cpd-opportunity-well-received-in-stanley/">Swimming Coach CPD Opportunity Well Received in Stanley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Twenty coaches from across the Swim England North East Region attended a CPD opportunity which focused on supporting and developing  the nutrition and psychology needs of their athletes.</p>
<p>The two sessions were delivered by specialists from the Swim England Talent Team. One coach commented, &#8220;Both presenters were very easy to follow and gave some useful &#8216;food for thought&#8217;. The information will definitely help empower my swimmers and parents so that my goals have the best chance of coming to fruition.&#8221;</p>
<p>The information from both sessions is available to view at:</p>
<p>Sports Nutrition: <a href="http://bit.ly/NER-coaches-2019">http://bit.ly/NER-coaches-2019</a></p>
<p>Sports Psychology: <a href="http://asaner.org.uk/mdocs-posts/coach-cpd-workshop-2019/">Coach CPD Workshop 2019</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/swimming-coach-cpd-opportunity-well-received-in-stanley/">Swimming Coach CPD Opportunity Well Received in Stanley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
